<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>

	<content contentuid="h5e8c0606g3c8fg4565g8e36g23936f2a9b5b" version="1">Our Lady of the Forest</content>	
	<content contentuid="h43050b60g1df5g407egb07aga2d2c4a91884" version="1">&lt;p&gt;Gentle Lady of the Forest, Mielikki, Guardian of Wild Places,&lt;br&gt;Blessed are the leaves that rustle in your sacred breeze,&lt;br&gt;Guide us through the shadows of the ancient trees.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keeper of the Woodlands, watchful and wise,&lt;br&gt; Grant us the strength to protect nature&apos;s prize.&lt;br&gt; As the moonlight bathes the forest floor,&lt;br&gt; Illuminate our path with your wisdom evermore.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the embrace of your serene realm,&lt;br&gt; We pledge to honor and protect, steadfast at the helm.&lt;br&gt; Grant us harmony with flora and fauna, great and small,&lt;br&gt; Mielikki, we humbly heed your timeless call.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;May the song of the wilderness be our guide,&lt;br&gt; And may your presence ever by our side.&lt;br&gt; Blessed Mielikki, Lady of the Grove,&lt;br&gt; In your grace, we find solace and love.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we tread upon the sacred ground,&lt;br&gt; May our actions echo the harmonious sound.&lt;br&gt; Honor to you, Mielikki, in whispers we pray,&lt;br&gt; Guide us through the forest, both night and day.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;More poetic prayers are penned, along with a small sketch of a unicorn in the margins.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
	
	<content contentuid="h420639ecgd996g4c52ga6aag6ee436d43ad7" version="1">The Gleaming Dragon</content>	
	<content contentuid="h6cf12c75g064ag4ff2gb1fbg75d41cfb25e8" version="1">&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Majestic Bahamut, Platinum Dragon of Radiant Light,&lt;br&gt; In the shadow of your wings, I find strength and might.&lt;br&gt; With scales of noble silver and eyes that gleam,&lt;br&gt; I stand before you, a dragonborn in your esteemed dream.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oh, Righteous One, embodiment of justice so pure,&lt;br&gt; Guide me through challenges, make my purpose sure.&lt;br&gt; Grant me the courage to face darkness with grace,&lt;br&gt; In your name, I find solace, in your wings, embrace.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;May my breath echo your righteous flame,&lt;br&gt; As I invoke your name, Bahamut, I proclaim.&lt;br&gt; Protector of the weak, guardian of the just,&lt;br&gt; In your presence, I place my unwavering trust.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Platinum Dragon, hear this plea,&lt;br&gt; Guide me, Bahamut, in your noble decree.&lt;br&gt; In your radiant light, may my path be clear,&lt;br&gt; Forever bound to you, without a trace of fear.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amen, oh Bahamut, in your glory divine,&lt;br&gt; In your name, this humble dragonborn shall shine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;There is a smudge of chromatic ink at the edge of the page.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; </content>
	
	<content contentuid="hf2ad1fd5g31adg4908g8393ga46ceaec49b3" version="1">First of the Seldarine</content>	
	<content contentuid="h4244aefeg8e81g409eg85cfg6f40eca40c09" version="1">&lt;p&gt;Luminous Corellon Larethian, Coronal of Arvandor,&lt;br&gt;In your radiance, we discover a realm without dictate.&lt;br&gt;From the loom of creation, we arise,&lt;br&gt;Children of beauty, breaking earthly ties.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preserver of Life, shaping form and light,&lt;br&gt;Bestow upon us wisdom, guide us through the night.&lt;br&gt;Beneath the moon&apos;s celestial art,&lt;br&gt;May our spirits transcend, free and unbound from the start.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bearer of the Silver Sword, guardian of elven might,&lt;br&gt;Grant us strength and courage against the Spider Queen&apos;s spite.&lt;br&gt;In the fluidity of form, beyond binaries we find,&lt;br&gt;A spectrum of truth, in your design entwined&lt;br&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Corellon, whose essence transcends bounds,&lt;br&gt;In your presence, acceptance resounds.&lt;br&gt;Guide us through realms, both near and far,&lt;br&gt;In life&apos;s dance, beneath your eternal star.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;A small child&apos;s drawing of an elf is scratched on the corner of this prayer sheet.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>	
	
	
		<!--Head start, be kind and add more after you use templates-->
	
	<!--COPY THIS AND EDIT-->
	<content contentuid="NEWHANDLE1" version="1">TITLE HERE</content>	
	<content contentuid="NEWHANDLE2" version="1">TEXT HERE</content>	
	<!--COPY THIS AND EDIT-->


</contentList>
